

<FullStack_Developer>

ABOUT ME!

I have a unique story to share, with a varied career and wealth of experience. Starting in construction and then moving to hospitality before transitioning to IT. I value hard work and dedication, and combining my practical skills with my interest in innovation and problem-solving has been a fulfilling experience. I am committed to learning and adapting to the rapid changes in the IT industry.

My diverse background gives me a unique perspective that I'm excited to bring to my next challenge.

Let's grow together!

EDUCATION

Amazon Web Services (AWS)

AWS re/Start Program Learner -Jun 2023 - Jul 2023

Code for All

Junior FullStack Developer -Jan 2023 - Apr 2023

Qualidade de Basto

High School Diploma -Nov 2002 - Dec 2005

EXPERIENCE

DEVELOPER

Freelancer

2023-present

- A Rest API library
- Technologies: Java, Spring Boot, Jira, Docker, Flyway, Gradle, Postman, Github

WAITER

Pastry South Africa

2017 - 2020

... (Linkedin)

CERTIFICATIONS







<Moisés Gonçalves_>

CONTACTS

https://www.linkedin.com/in/moises-goncalves-dev/

https://moisesgoncalves86.github.io/My-Portfolio/

http://github.com/moisesgoncalves86

+351 916 762 102

moisesgoncalves1986@gmail.com

Portugal

SKILLS

Java

Spring Boot

Rest APIs

MySQL

JavaScript

GitHub

Spring Framework
CSS

Junit

Mockito

AWS Cloud

OOP

Maven

JQuery

Docker

Bootstrap

HTML

Jira Software

PROJECTS

- API for a library catalog (Spring Boot)
- API for deliveries (Spring Boot)
- RunPoorCadet (Java game)
- Map Editor (Java App)
- MyPortfolio(Js, HTML, CSS)

LANGUAGES

- Portuguese
- **English**
- Spanish
- French

HOBBIES

- Cycling
- F1
- Chess